<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SparkWomen</string>

    <array name="lawsBig">

        <item>Tunisian women have the right to marry and choose their own spouse.
            The minimum age for marriage is 18 for both men and women.
            Previously, the PSC allowed girls as young as 15 to marry with the
            permission of their male guardian, but this provision was repealed in 2017.
        </item>

        <item>Tunisian women have the right to divorce their husbands under certain conditions, such as abuse or neglect. A woman may also seek divorce if her
            husband is absent for a long period of time or has abandoned the family.
        </item>
        <item>
            Tunisian women have the right to custody of their children in the event of divorce or the death of their husband. However, if the mother remarries,
            custody may be transferred to the new husband if he agrees to take on this responsibility.
        </item>
        <item>Tunisian women have the right to inherit property from their parents and spouse. In 2018,
            Tunisia became the first country in the Arab world to enact a law that guarantees equal inheritance rights for men and women.
        </item>
        <item>Tunisian women have the right to work and receive equal pay for equal work. Discrimination based on gender is prohibited by law. The Tunisian
            Labor Code also provides for maternity leave and breastfeeding breaks.
        </item>
        <item>Tunisian women have the right to access education and receive equal opportunities for education and training. The literacy
            rate for women in Tunisia is relatively high compared to other countries in the region.
        </item>
        <item>Tunisian women have the right to participate in politics and run for elected office. The country
            has a quota system that reserves a certain percentage of seats in parliament for women.
        </item>
        <item>Tunisian women have the right to access reproductive health services, including family planning and safe abortion. The government provides
            free or subsidized contraceptives and has established clinics that offer safe abortion services.
        </item>
        <item>Tunisian women have the right to protection from gender-based violence, including sexual harassment and domestic violence.
            The law criminalizes such acts and provides for legal remedies and support services for victims.
        </item>
        <item>Tunisian women have the right to freedom of expression and association, including the right to form and join organizations and express their opinions freely.
            Tunisia is known for its relatively liberal political and social climate, although some restrictions on freedom of expression remain.
        </item>
    </array>
</resources>